Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you!
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, it's so elusive?
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me!
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you!
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see!
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
Believe in what I do!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We live how we want to.
There is no limit to us!
We have the power of love.
We don't want to live ordinary lives.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We live in one another.
Move it! Get out of our way! Step aside!
Hey, isn't that...
No, Chaka, please wait!
So who are they?
The Guardians.
The Kicking Claw Force.
Don't attack, men.
You'll only be throwing your lives away.
They broke the door down. Adari, move.
Please, save His Majesty
and Princess Phoebe.
Your Majesty, defending you to
the death is not only our mission.
It is the highest honor and privilege.
Therefore, we can't simply avoid him.
He is one of the seven
warlords of the sea.
The only way to beat
him is to fight dirty.
We four are as one.
We fight for your honor.
To set things right.
It seems that you have
quite the reputation.
Therefore, I will spare your lives.
Leave now and go home.
We can't do that.
There is another reason
we will not withdraw.
Reason?
If the rumors are true and
you really are the ringleader,
the architect of this whole rebellion...
Those bruises.
What have you men done?
Shall I?
You needn't waste your
time on these cretins.
They didn't.
Chaka, what's happening to their bodies?
I fear to temporarily
increase their power.
They drank the fatal elixir.
It grants incredible strength,
but then kills the host.
They're dead men. Oh no!
You bulked up to challenge
me, I'm flattered.
But what good is victory if
you're not around to enjoy it?
Chaka, please,
forgive us for doing this
without consulting you,
but we had to take drastic measures
to end this country's suffering.
those idiots how could they we
have to make him realize the fury of
This country!
That wasn't the smartest decision.
A person should value
his life above all else.
But it's too late for regrets, yes?
And if you're all going to die anyway, I
don't have to bother killing you myself,
right?
You don't even have the decency to fight!
Chaka, I'm sorry.
Behold the very definition of stupidity.
You bastard!
Chaka!
Chaka, this is senseless.
You'll just be following
them to their deaths.
Ah, they're a zone type.
I see you share the same flaws
these fools you'll die for others
Damn it.
Lost too much, Willett.
Yes, I should be thankful the cuts aren't
that deep, but it does hurt like ow.
Wonder how the others are doing.
Want to know what's going on.
Idiots better not be dead.
What?
What do you mean I have
to pair with eyelash?
Look, he's a camel!
I'm very fragile so I need
someone who can back me up
Man up the raffle was fair.
You got eyelash and that's that fine But
you better promise me one thing when me
and this stupid camel are standing at the
doorway of death Please
come to our rescue. Sorry.
I only save the damsels.
You're on your own
Hey, what's wrong? Usopp?
Why are you crying?
Yeah, you're crying, yeah, he who
smelt the dilded, yeah, that's it,
you dilded, you dilded,
you dilded, you dilded, you're a dilded, a
dilded smelter, that old hag said, Luffy,
she said Luffy's dead,
so I, I wonder if it's true, come on,
you guys really believe that,
of course not, Luffy's alive,
what do you think we are, stupid,
that's right, I don't believe
it either, Luffy is alive,
yeah, all right, I get it, you're
preaching to the choir here?
What we have to do now is
get to the palace ASAP!
Now if you don't mind,
try to plug your snot at least until
the rumbling from the battle stops!
Don't swallow it!
Thank you everyone!
You're welcome!
But it's too early to thank us!
He's right!
Besides, if you really
want to thank pirates you?
They have to let us see some goods.
Nami, what is it you're trying to
leech out of this country anyway?
Is Nami okay?
Did she manage to get away?
They finally came off.
Calling it a powerful one-shot attack, I
think that's a bit of an understatement.
The fighting's come far.
They're right there,
just around the corner.
Guess the situation's changed.
Anyway, I better get to the palace.
Sounds like the battle's started.
What about Vivi?
Oh, yeah. One more thing.
And this is an important fact to remember.
After a battle, these guys
put down a ton of food.
Okay.
We'll be waiting for you!
This is absolutely crucial.
Don't screw this up!
Let's go!
See you at the palace!
Chaka!
Weakness is a crime, punishable by death.
Phoebe!
No, Koza.
Koza.
It's you.
Oh, I see you came through
the shortcut you used to use.
This can't be.
What am I seeing here?
I came in hope of persuading
the royal army, but...
Chaka, and the king is about to
be killed by this country's hero.
I can't believe my eyes.
Now things are starting
to get interesting.
Here we are in the midst of an epic war,
and yet the leaders of both
sides aren't on the battlefield.
Fate has placed them
squabbling at my feet.
A battle to the death
between two broken titans
bleeding out the last
remnants of their power.
You seem lost and confused.
Don't worry, it's a natural reaction.
Let me help you.
Relax and open your mind, then imagine being
faced with the worst possible scenario.
Koza, purge your heart of all suspicion!
Do you love this country?
This is my home.
Mine as well.
Koza, listen.
Vivi, who was responsible for the
drought ravaging this country? Tell me?
It was that honor belongs to me!
Over the past two years
each and every malicious
deed you attributed to the
king's doing was in fact?
Perpetrated by my company a trap that
saw you playing right into our hands.
It was a flawless systematic
plot of deception.
I Must say it was entertaining
watching as the royal
family and its mighty army
desperately chased our shadows
Pity.
You probably would have died in ignorant
bliss not knowing these brutal facts.
Koza, listen!
Majesty.
There's still some time
if you have the courage.
You must act now.
Save as many citizens as you can.
In less than half an hour, the whole palace
square will be blown to kingdom come.
What do you mean?
So you're still alive, are you?
Hurry!
Stop!
Vivi!
Get off of me!
What are you doing?
There's no time!
The battle is about to
spill into the square.
If it's really set to blow up, get off!
You have to listen to me!
Think this through, please!
What will happen if you tell the
armies the square is set to explode?
The men will panic!
It would only add more
chaos to the battle,
and even if you stop the bomb,
it won't stop the fighting!
Either way, people are still going to die!
You won't save anyone!
Understand?
Huh.
Well, well, what a perceptive girl.
Our only hope is to do what should
have been done from the start.
We have to stop the rebellion
and end this bloodshed!
And you...
You're the only one who can do it!
Did you really think I
was going to sit back and
watch passively while you
tried to ruin my plans?
Chaka!
I am Alabaster's guardian deity.
I am the Jackal.
I'll fight as long as there
is breath left in my body.
Some call that brave, I call it stupid.
Do what you must, both of you.
I will hold him back
for a few more minutes.
Chaka, such a shame the leader
of the Sansan clan is so weak.
Boy, what's the matter?
What's wrong with you?
I'm a child.
You can't treat me like this.
You're a pain in the neck, kid.
Koza, you asked me to train you,
or have you forgotten that already?
Report from Guard Unit 2 to Headquarters!
Report from Unit 2 to Headquarters!
Line four has been breached!
Enemy has broken through!
The rebel army is
currently passing through
the central plaza heading
to the north block!
They will reach the palace!
Raise the flag to surrender!
Royal army, you will
surrender immediately!
Princess of Evie, is she serious? But why?
That's absurd.
If we do as she says, that would
mean the end of this country.
Hey, look! That's...
It's Koza!
What is the rebel army's leader
doing here in the palace?
Hear me, the princess speaks the truth!
We no longer desire victory,
only to end this conflict!
Both sides have spilled enough blood!
I will make each and every rebel understand
the pointlessness of this civil war!
They will see, as I do, that we
no longer have reason to fight!
In the interest of restoring
peace and preserving life,
I ask you, wave the white flag! Please!
The king's head will roll this day!
Oh, I can see the clock tower up ahead!
We're approaching the palace square!
Prepare to attack!
Wait! Stop!
White flags?
The royal army is waving white flags!
We did it!
They surrender!
It's Koza!
The battle is over!
Sir, everyone, quiet your
anger and lower your weapons.
The royal army will stand down.
Let no more blood stain the streets.
Please, listen to him.
Is this the truth, Koza?
Yes.
The battle's finally over.
Cousin!
You just wait until it's finished.
This town will bring good fortune
and joy to so many people.
It's going to be the best town ever.
When it's up and running, I'll
personally give you the grand tour.
Don't fight Rebel Army.
Don't fight them.
How can they shoot Koza? Get them!
It's the rough works!
What did you do?
Why did you shoot?
Listen to me now, Rebel Army.
Do not fight.
What's going on?
Where'd the sandstorm come from?
Listen, Rebel Army.
They're shooting at us.
How dare they?
Where did all the sand
come from so suddenly?
We can't see anything.
Damn it! Bastards!
Don't shoot carelessly!
What's going on?
They still don't know what's happening.
What's going on, you idiots,
is that Baroque Works members are
posing as soldiers in both your armies.
Stop now!
Come on, just hang in there!
They aren't surrendering.
Thought they'd ambush us by
raising a phony white flag, huh?
So this is how the
Royal Army plans to win.
By using dirty tricks like that!
Stop it!
No, don't do this!
Please, stop fighting!
Soldiers!
Look up here!
Stop, Rebel Army.
Stop this.
This battle is...
Hey, are you okay? Damn.
Now, Royal Army, launch counter-attack!
Stop it!
Stop fighting!
Please don't fight.
Stop now!
You fought long and hard,
princess, and did well.
But now...
Give up.
Your voice will no longer
reach them so this is it.
You have to run away vv get away
from him before it's too late!
I won't.
You made this dust, devil.
It's your doing, isn't it?
But still, there's time.
If I stop the explosion that's
scheduled in 15 minutes,
I can still reduce the
number of casualties.
If I try this, the rebellion will stop.
If I try that, the rebellion will stop.
It's time to wake up, princess.
I'm tired of your useless idealism.
It's gotten pathetic.
What good are your happy ideals if you
can't do anything to make them reality?
Then they're nothing but dreams.
And your dreams don't stand a chance.
I don't care what you think of my ideals.
I'm never going to give up on them!
You would never understand!
I'm this country's
princess, I won't give up!
I won't give in no matter what!
You really are a sad little girl.
I refuse...
to give up!
I will save Alamaster!
Alamaster!
VV!
You have only fifteen minutes
until the square is blown up.
More of the rebel forces are
gathering as reinforcements arrive.
One after another, without even realizing
they're marching to their death.
You know, you could have let the Royal Army
know about the coming explosion earlier.
If so, maybe there
would have been a panic.
But then you could have saved tens
of thousands of innocent lives.
Stop it!
Please, crocodile!
Just let her go!
In the end, your plans for saving this
country have done more harm than good.
Your wretched failures
have only ended up hurting
the precious citizens
who you love so dearly.
From the beginning of my operations here,
the sheer stupidity of
your country has amused me.
So pathetic, so easy to manipulate!
You did a decent job of spying on
our company for the past two years,
I will grant you that much?
It's me, Vivi.
Don't you recognize me?
I look different.
I lost some weight, I suppose.
But when it was all said and done, you
really had no hope of changing anything.
Stopping the rebellion.
Saving the kingdom.
All those worthless ideas
you've clung to for so long.
In the end, they just
created more victims for me.
Let me tell you something.
You're never going to save this country!
Goodbye, princess.
Ah ha ha ha ha...
It can't be.
Crocodile!
Luffy!
It can't be!